[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "During pregnancy the following symptoms happen to what part of the body: grow larger, tender, swollen, and darkened areolas.", "correct_answer": "Breast", "incorrect_answers": ["Hands", "Stomach", "Face"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Samuel Adams Triple Bock, produced by the Boston Beer Company, reaches what percentage of alcohol by volume?", "correct_answer": "17%", "incorrect_answers": ["12%", "9%", "23%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor uttered the phrase Carpe diem. Seize the day, boys. Make your lives extraordinary in the 1989 movie Dead Poets Society?", "correct_answer": "Robin Williams", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Hanks", "Tim Robbins", "Ethan Hawke"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first credit card?", "correct_answer": "Diners Club", "incorrect_answers": ["Kresges Green Card", "Carte Blanc", "American Express"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where was Leroys master going to visit his mother in the movie The Last Dragon?", "correct_answer": "Miami", "incorrect_answers": ["New york", "Seattle", "San Diego"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ironically the song Video Killed the Radio Star by the Buggles was the first video played on MTV in the USA. Which was the second song aired on the Music Television?", "correct_answer": "Pat Benatar, You Better Run", "incorrect_answers": ["Madonna, Like a Virgin", "Dire Straits, Money for Nothing", "Michael Jackson, Thriller"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ishmael Boorg, a character from the movie Kingpin, bowled against Ernie McCracken in the finals of the Reno Open.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This satellite, launched from Cape Canaveral on January 31, 1958, by the Jupiter-C vehicle, was the first United States Earth satellite.", "correct_answer": "Explorer I", "incorrect_answers": ["Titan I", "Gemini I", "Apollo I"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Sin City character saves Hartigan from dying of multiple gunshot wounds?", "correct_answer": "Senator Roark", "incorrect_answers": ["Becky", "Nancy Callahan", "His partner, Bob"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rays and Skates are types of sharks.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Saturn is visible without any optical aid.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what city of Oregon was the movie The Goonies set and filmed in?", "correct_answer": "Astoria", "incorrect_answers": ["Ashland", "Oregon City", "Salem"]}]